Guide to the United Telegraph Workers Records WAG.144
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series V: Convention Proceedings
  - CTU Convention bills, resolutions, minutes (annotated) proceedings, officers reports, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - CTU Convention (28th Reg. Convention) proceedings, officers reports, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - CTU Convention minutes, resolutions, reports (annotated), 1959 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - CTU Convention Bills, IEB reports, Committee reports, minutes post Convention, IEB, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - CTU Convention (29th Reg. Convention) proceedings, officers reports, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - CTU International Convention reports, bills, misc., 1961 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - CTU Convention (30th Reg. Convention) proceedings, officers reports, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - CTU Convention minutes. reports, bills, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - CTU Convention (31 st Reg. Convention) proceedings. officers reports, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - CTU Convention minutes, resolutions, bills, reports, notes, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - UTW Convention (32nd Reg. Convention) officers reports, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - UTW Convention (33rd Reg. Convention); proceedings, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - "Convention resolutions" petitions, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Convention Local 48 petitions, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - UTW Convention (34th International Convention); proceedings, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - UTW Convention (35th Reg. Convention); proceedings, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - UTW Convention (36th International Convention); proceedings, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - UTW Convention (37th International Convention); proceedings, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Convention re organization; correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Convention Re organization; correspondence, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Convention re organization, 1986 correspondence, #2 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - 1986 Convention re organization; (#3 July September), 1986-1986 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - 1986 Convention re organization; proceedings, agendas, reports, resolutions, 1986-1986 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Special Convention; reports, committees, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Special Convention; proceedings, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Special Convention; resolutions (book, other), Apr 1986 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Convention re organization; Board Orders, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Convention re organization; delegates, offices, UAW merger proposal, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Special Convention; by laws, credentials, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Local UTW, 1928-1996 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Convention re organization; Notes, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Convention re organization; background, documents, correspondence, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - UTW Special Convention (38th International Convention October'86), 1986 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Special Convention UTW proceedings, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - UTW Convention (39th International Convention); proceedings, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - CWA/UTW Bargaining Council; proceedings First Regular Convention, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - CWA/UTW proceedings, officers reports; 7 Bargaining Council Second Reg. Conv, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - CWA/UTW Bargaining Council 2nd Convention Resolutions, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - CWA/UTW Bargaining Council proceedings Special Convention, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - proceedings, officers reports; 3rd.Annual Convention Western Union Division CTU AFL, 1942 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence reports, greetings, Western Union Div., CTU Convention, 1942 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Western Union Div. CTU Convention; correspondence, reports, delegates' credentials, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - CTU AFL Western Union Div. officers reports, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - proceedings, officers reports, other; Western Union Div. Fifth Annual Convention, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Convention proceedings, officers reports, CTU Western Union Div. other, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Convention proceedings, officers reports, other CTU Western Union Div., 1947 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Convention proceedings, officers reports; CTU Western Union Div., 1948 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Convention transcripts; bills, credentials, other; CTU Western Union Div., 1948 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Convention proceedings, officers reports, other; CTU Western Union Div., 1949 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Convention proceedings, officers reports; CTU Western Union Div., 1951 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Proposed Amendments, resolutions, appeals convention; CTU Western Union Div., 1951 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Convention minutes, delegates, lists, credentials; CTU Western Union Div., 1951 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence (1950 1951); CTU Western Union Div. Convention (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Resolutions; other CTU Western Union Div., 1951 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Convention proceedings, officers reports, CTU Western Union Div., 1953 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Convention proposed amendments; CTU Western Union Div., 1953 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Resolutions, 1 91; 93 206; CTU Western Union Div., 1953 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Resolutions #207 280; Agenda items approved, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Convention minutes; Special Convention minutes October 21, 1953; with Amalgamation Agreement (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - correspondence, delegates lists, reports, credentials; CTU Western Union Div. Convention, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Convention proceedings, officers reports; CTU Western Union Convention, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Resolutions, appeals, correspondence; CTU VVU Div. Convention, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Resolutions; CTU Western Union Div. Convention, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Contract resolutions; CTU Western Union Div. Convention, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Minutes, reports, proceedings, delegates, committees, credentials; CTU Western Union Div. Convention, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Convention proceedings, officers reports, program; CTU Western Union Div. Convention, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Committee reports, drafts; CTU Western Union Div. Convention, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Resolutions, drafts; CT U Western Union, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - By laws, Resolutions Book, CTU Western Union Convention, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Contract Resolutions Book; CTU Western Union Div,. Convention, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Convention correspondence, telegrams, notes; CTU Western Union Div., 1957 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Delegates lists, credentials, correspondence; CTU Western Union Div. Convention, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Convention proceedings, officers reports; CTU Western Union Div. Convention, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - 1959 Convention Correspondence, 1957, 1958, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Convention CTU Western Union; Resolutions Book, annotated, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Resolutions Book, annotated, notes, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Contract Resolutions Book, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Contract Resolutions Book (annotated), 1959 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Convention Minneapolis Convention Brochures, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Convention proceedings, officers reports CTU Western Union, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Resolutions Book, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Contract Resolutions Book, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - (1960 1961); correspondence CTU Western Union (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - preliminary credentials; Convention materials CTU Western Union, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Speech, draft CTU Western Union Convention, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Greetings to Convention; Announcements, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Program flyers, Convention delegates info., 1961 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Charter, revisions Convention CTU Western Union, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Reports, resolutions; CTU Western Union Convention, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Reports and resolutions, approved (CTU Western Union Convention), 1961 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Bills, resolutions; CTU Western Union Div. Convention, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Reports to the Convention, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Convention proceedings, officers reports, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - proceedings, notes, telegrams, correspondence, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Reports and Resolutions Book, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Resolutions Book, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Reports, resolutions, correspondence, drafts; credentials, other, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Convention proceedings, officers reports; CTU Western Union Convention, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Resolutions Book, 1928-1996 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Contract Resolutions Book, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Proceedings, resolutions, correspondence, arrangements w/ notes, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Convention Extra notes, reports, credentials, ballot, index, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Convention proceedings, officers reports, credentials, other, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Resolutions Book, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Contract Resolutions Book, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Convention proceedings, correspondence, arrangements, notes, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Convention proceedings, officers reports, credentials, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Resolutions. Book UTW Western Union Div., 1969 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Contract Resolutions Book UTW VVU Div., 1969 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - UTW minutes Convention mailed for approval, 1928-1996 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - correspondence, notes, reports, proceedings, credentials., 1969 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - proceedings, all correspondence, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - UTW Western Union Convention; officers reports, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Convention proceedings, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Convention Resolutions Book, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Contract Resolutions Book, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Series VI: Indexed Arbitrations
  - Arbitrations Index #3 A, 1928-1996 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Arbitrations, 1949-1953 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Arbitrations #19 39, 1928-1996 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Arbitrations #40 58, 1928-1996 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Arbitrations #59 70, 1928-1996 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Arbitrations #71 82, 1928-1996 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Arbitrations #83 90, 1928-1996 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Arbitrations #91 100, 1928-1996 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Arbitrations #101 118, 1928-1996 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Arbitrations #119 125, 1928-1996 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Arbitrations #121 136, 1928-1996 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Arbitrations #137 145, 1928-1996 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Arbitrations #146 155, 1928-1996 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Arbitrations #156 163, 1928-1996 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Arbitrations #165 177, 1928-1996 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Arbitrations #178 184, 1928-1996 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Arbitrations #185 196, 1928-1996 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Arbitrations # 197 207, 1928-1996 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Arbitrations #208 220, 1928-1996 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Arbitrations #221 229, 1928-1996 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Arbitrations #230 237, 1928-1996 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Series VII: Collective Bargaining Materials
  The bulk of the materials in the series relates to the effort to implement a job classification system through collective bargaining. Western Union successfully avoided this standard corporate practice until the 1940's. While collective bargaining materials related to other employers such as the Bendix Field Engineering Company (satellite tracking at Goddard Space Center, near Washington, D.C) is included, the bulk of the materials relate to Western Union. Collective bargaining materials related to the divisions are included (e.g., Canadian; Press). Strike materials (bulletins, correspondence, press releases) are included in this section. Two boxes at the end of the series contain Exhibit materials, and Western Union bargaining records, 1946-1949, originating with CWA District 6 (Texas).
  The materials related to the 53 day strike in 1952 are of exceptional depth. Materials include correspondence, strike bulletins, notes, news clips, company and union financial data, and public relations materials, such as radio broadcasts.
  - Job Class. Bulletins;.#l, #36, Dec 1945-Sep 29, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - War Labor Board Award: #Postal Merger Case, 1944-1946 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Agreements, Western Union, 1945-1949 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Arbitrations Western Union National Coordinating Board AFL; CTU; ACA, 1928-1996 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Wages, rates, Job Classification Western Union 1940s (40 hour, night shift; differential), 1940-1949 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Job Classification Correspondence stipulations, other, 1945 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Job Classification correspondence, stipulations, other, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Job Classification correspondence, stipulations, other, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Job Classification correspondence, stipulations, other, 1948-1949 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Job Classification descriptions titles, levels, agreements, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Wage rates, Job Classification, 1946, 1947, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Job Classification, 1946, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Job Classification, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Job Classification, correspondence (Appendix B), 1949 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Job Classification, correspondence, 1950-1953 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Wage schedule Job Classification titles and descriptions, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Wage schedule Job Classification, 1952 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Minutes, notes, T. Freeman (40 hour work week), 1952 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Job Classification stipulations, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Job Classification correspondence (Appendix B), 1954 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Job Classification, wage schedule, 1954 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Job Classification correspondence (Appendix B), 1955-1956 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Contract correspondence; stipulations; ballot; strike vote, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Contract agenda; NBC bulletins (Job Classification, other), 1956-1957 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Contract agenda, Job Classification, other, 1956-1957 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Job Classification, (Jan. March) correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Job Classification (April), 1957-1958 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Job Classification correspondence (May July), 1957-1958 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Job Classification correspondence (August October), 1957-1958 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Job Classification correspondence (November-December'57, January'58), 1957-1958 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Bargaining stipulations (Western Union) (#1 57), 1957 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Bargaining stipulations (VV U) (#2 57), 1957 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Bargaining stipulations (Western Union) (#2 57) (#3 57), 1957 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Bargaining stipulations (Western Union), 1957 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Proposals, agreements, wage schedules (effective 1/1/57), 1957 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Job Classification Revision, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Job Classification (revision), 1957 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Contract agenda, National Bargaining Committee CTU, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Contract agenda, company work sheets, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Contract negotiations notes, correspondence, other, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Division and District; Headquarters Seniority list, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Stipulations #1 30, 1 23 '58, Dist. re organization; #2 58, 1 23 '58, Dist. Sales Program, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Appendix A, Job Classification Western Union, 1958-1960 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Job Classification revision, Part #1 1/1/1959 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Job Classification revisions, Part #2 1/1/1959 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Stip. #1 59 23 59; Transfer of Dist. headquarters to Div. headquarters, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Contract negotiations (correspondence, notes, other) #1 (1959 61 Documents), 1960 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - contract negotiations #2, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - contract negotiations #3, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Appendix B, correspondence (includes documents from 1954 1960), 1958, 1959, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Job Classification statistics, 1957-1960 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - correspondence, contracts, Job Classification and stipulations, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Stipulations. #2 60 Transfer of Work Chicago warehouse; #5 60 Switching Clerks #6 60 time keeping, clerical transfers, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Stip. #1 61 Computer Center Tech. Apprentice, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Stip 7/27/1961 #2 61, Re classification of job tides: Printer; Maintainer to Plant Maintainer (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - stipulations. re alignments of Reperforator Centers, NBC; meeting; San Francisco, November 7/13/62, notes, subsequent correspondence, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - stipulations; NBC and Co. meetings, June. 10 21, 1963; Stip. 1) overseas bonus amendment 2 63, 3 63, 4 63 2) Western Union sales Department re organization 3) Field Engineers dilution 4) Relief Microwave Maintainer (signed copies) (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Stipulations establishment of Reg'I offices and Reperforator re alignment, notes, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Stipulations. St. 1 65 Regional offices (April 3, 1965); additional company credit for early retirement Stip. 2 65 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Stip. AUTODIN (3/11/66); (notes on meetings with Galbreath), 1966 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Stip. Establishment of the Western Union Material Management Department; Home Office NYC August 8, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Stipulations. 1) Stipulation #3 67 co service credits for early retirement 10/6/67, signed copy 2) Stipulation #4 67 (signed copy) notes: NBC Co. meeting November 20, 1967; Edits Friday payday (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Stipulations, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Stipulations #3 68 proposed (seniority lists of affected districts), 1968 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Job Classification, negotiations work sheets; (Los Angeles) #1, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Job Classification negotiations work sheets (L.A. #2), 1969 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Dist. of Jobs, Job Classification Fund L.A. (1/28/69 2/28/69), 1969 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Job Classification negotiations (Stips. 1 69; 2 69 and 3 69), 1969 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Job Classification negotiations #2 L.A. (proposal notes), 1969 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Job Classification negotiations #3 (Hand written notes), 1969 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Stipulations. #7 69 mechanization of book keeping functions; #8 69 Transfer of telephone recording work to Mt. Vernon, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Stipulations. (#I); 19/14 1 69, 2 69, 3 69, 4 69: Amendments to 3 68, Billing and mechanization, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Stipulations. 1969 (#2), 5 69 TWX Acquisition (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Stip. #3; Stip. 8 69; notes, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Stipulations #1, #5, 4 70 through #14 70; Oct 5, 1970 uncompleted CCC, CTB (Centralized Telephone Bureau), CSP Nov 6, 1970 Mailgram. (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Stipulations. #2, #5 70, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - contract negotiations, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - contract negotiations, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - contract negotiations statistics, correspondence, other, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - contract negotiations (bulletins, press, contract, flyers), 1971 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - stipulations. # 1 71; 2 71; 3 71, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - negotiations on. mechanization, bookkeeping stipulations #2 72; R. C. Brockert, N.V.P. correspondence, 5/1/72, 2/2/73, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - negotiations on mechanization stipulations (R. C. Brockert), 1972 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Stipulations. stip #1 72, Early Retirement Plan #2 72 Area Mechanization Program (cashier, credit, collection, bookkeeping, consolidation, mechanization), 1972 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Co. Job Classification Proposal (revised), ??? July 17, 1973; R. C. Brockert #1 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Co. Job Classification Proposal #2, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Co. and NBC contract negotiations notes (R. C. Brockert) #1, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - notes #2 contract negotiations, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - notes #3 contract negotiations, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - contract agreement #1 Stip. 3 73 and 4 73 (amendments and changes; N.V.P. Brockert), 1973 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Stip. #2, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Stip. #3, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Contract negotiations Book #1 (a), 1973 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Contract negotiations Book #1 (b), 1973 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Contract negotiations Book #2 (a), 1973 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Contract negotiations Book #2 (b), 1973 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Economic Stabilization, Phase III Cost of Living Council (CLQ, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Contract negotiations Job Classification changes R. C. Brockert, Oct 1972 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Notes (b) changes Job Classification (R. Brockert), 1973 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Negotiations Job Classification (a), 1973 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Negotiations Job Classification (b), 1973 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Stipulations #4 73 Rates, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - NBC #1 NBC matters and contract amendments, 1974-1975 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - NBC NBC matters and contract amendments, 1974-1975 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - NBC NBC matters and contract amendments, 1974-1975 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - NBC (NBC actions completed #1 EEOC subsidiaries, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - NBC (NBC Acts #2), 1974-1975 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - NBC, 1974-1975 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - NBC, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - NBC, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Contract negotiations, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Contract negotiations notes (IBC and Co. (a)), 1976 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Contract negotiations notes (b), 1976 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Contract negotiations notes (c), 1976 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Contract negotiations notes (handwritten), 1976 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Contract negotiations IBC minutes, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Contract agreement dental plan (see IBC Bulletin #9, August 3, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - NBC #1 (matters handled), 1976-1977 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - NBC #2 (matters handled), 1976-1977 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - NBC #3 (matters handled), 1976-1977 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - IBC, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - IBC, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Contract negotiations (Brockert), 1979 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Contract negotiations, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Contract negotiations, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Contract (Western Union/VTV), 1979 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - IBC Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - IBC Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - IBC Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Contract negotiations UTW Bargaining Unit; Employees Western Union (R. C. Brockert), 1982 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - UTW Western Union Contract Negotiations (Co. Discontinued Public; Services Marketing Plan), 1982 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - #1 83 organization changes and national transfers Article 22, 1983-1985 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Contract negotiations Correspondence, memos, bulletins, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Contract negotiations #2 Data, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Contract negotiations Task Force; Reductions in work force (10% wage reduction), 1985 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - IBC notes (#I); Bargaining UTW/Western Union, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - IBC notes #2 UTW/Western Union, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - IBC notes #3, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Contract negotiations UTW/Western Union minutes, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Contract Bulletins, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Strike Authorization Ballot, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Assessment, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Contract ratification, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Contract negotiations ratification, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - UTW/Western Union contract ratification, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Contract negotiations UTW/Western Union #1 CWA Bargaining Council, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Contract negotiations #2 CWA Bargaining Council, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Contract ratification Western Union referendum Contract and strike, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Western Union Printout contract ratification, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 17)